

Aman Yadav

UG Student, B.Tech CSE (2023)

PROFILE

Address Ghaziabad, Uttar Pradesh

Phone Number +91-9717617021

Website

https://yadav-aman.github.io

Email Address

amansy04@gmail.com

Date Of Birth 26 December 1999

Linkedin aman-yadav07

Github

yadav-aman

AWARDS AND ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Toycathon June **Finalist** 2021

Govt. Of India

Deans List November Shiv Nadar 2020 University

HCL Hackathon

July Winner 2020 **HCL**

Ideonator AIC-SNU

November 2019

IICDC Govt. of India

March 2019

CERTIFICATIONS

Google IT

Automation with September 2020 **Python**

Coursera

A 6 course specialization offered by Google on coursera

LANGUAGES

English

Hindi

Fluent

Native Tongue

Punjabi

Familiar

HOBBIES

Badminton

Travelling

Art

Coding

Digital Art and Illustrations

ABOUT ME

A self motivated student, developer and a lifelong learner with an open and inquisitive mind. I love to code, and I'm inclined towards open-source technology and cybersecurity. I am always open for new challenges and opportunities. I am a team player and always willing to step up as a leader. Some of my key strengths are:

- Hands on programming experience in Python
- Commitment, determination and problem solving skills to execute a task to completion
- Familiarity with *nix Operating systems and Relational databases
- Aptitude for automation, information security and software development

WORK EXPERIENCE

Aggrow

(June 2021 - Present)

Web Development Intern

Startup Based on food supply chain optimization

Google Developer Student Club -

(September 2021 -SNU Present)

Web Development Mentor

Go Green - SNU (November 2020 - September 2021)

Marketing and Design Team

A social and environmental club which aims at a cleaner and greener society.

Blue Circle - SNU

(September 2020 - August 2021)

Volunteer

Peer support guide to help freshmen getting accustomed with the university

EDUCATION

(July 2019 - Present) Shiv Nadar University

8.88 CGPA **Bachelors** Computer Science & Engineering

New Era School 10 CGPA

10+2 Schooling

SKILLS

Python Java

Git Linux

C/C++ **JavaScript**

HTML/CSS **DBMS**

PROJECTS

Food-Ez

https://github.com/yadav-aman/food-ez

Contact-less food ordering with customers and inventory management. With react front-end and FastAPI(python) backend.

CodeForces Helper

https://github.com/yadav-aman/codeforces-helper

Web scraping and Automation script to help with codeforces test cases.

Flask Based Ecommerce Site

https://github.com/yadav-aman/HCL-HackathonQ2

Fully functional flask based Ecommerce site with recommendation system.

2-3 Tree Visualizer

https://github.com/yadav-aman/TwoThreeTree

Visual representation of 2-3 Tree using JavaFX.